Model by: Pitcherbe
Model name: Fnaf4Room v2.pmx, No roof ver.pmx
Copyright: Scott Cawthon
Description: The room/house where the FNaF 4 game takes place. This does not count any rooms shown in minigames.

Rules:
you can edit or take parts just credit me. 

you can redistribute the stage the parts and its edits just credit. 
If you take the main room wall texture please credit oscarthechinchilla. if that's all you're taking crediting me is optional since i only made minimal edits to it.

NO R-18 OR SEXUAL/SEXUALLY SUGGESTIVE CONTENT
Gore or a lot of violence is okay, but put a mature content filter on it if possible.

PLEASE CREDIT ME

If you use effects in video or picture renders of this stage, please credit the people who made those if you can. Its not often i see effect creators credited but they deserve it for making the things that improve our pictures and videos. This isnt absolutely required but it'd be polite.

don't use for commercial use/don't make money off of this, physical or digital.
DO NOT USE THIS IN PICTURE COMMISSIONS. YOU DID NOT MAKE THIS STAGE AND YOU HAVE NO RIGHT MAKING MONEY OFF OF IT.

Please credit me for making the building
Also
shoutout to oscarthechinchilla for converting/rigging/making textures for the robot toy  and making the room texture✌ 

Toon by: AceYoen

And also shoutout to testers and people who gave ideas for the update




One or more textures on this 3D model have been created with images from CGTextures.com. These images may not be redistributed by default, please visit www.cgtextures.com for more information.